A Guide to the Records of Jamestown 2007, 1986-2009
Library of Virginia
- Series IV: Project Documentation Files - Historically Significant, 2000-2008., Extent: 13 boxes. (Box 59-71)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Loudoun County, 2004-2008. (Box 63, Folder 52)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Louisa County, 2004-2008. (Box 63, Folder 53)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Lunenburg County, 2003-2008. (Box 63, Folder 54)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Luray, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 55)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Lynchburg, 2003-2008. (Box 63, Folder 56)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Madison County, 2005-2008. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Marion, 2004-2008. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Martinsville, Henry County, 2004-2008. (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Mathews County, 2005-2008. (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - McLean, Great Falls, 2002-2008. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Middlesex County, 2005-2008. (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Montgomery County, 2005-2008. (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Monumental United Methodist Church, 2006-2008. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Mount Vernon - Lee Chamber of Commerce, 2005-2008. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Mount Zion Baptist Church, Alvaton, Georgia County, 2005-2008. (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Naval Station Norfolk, 2006-2008. (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Naval Weapons Station, Yorktown, 2006-2008. (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Nelson County, 2003-2008. (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - New Castle, Craig County, 2005-2008. (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Newport News, 2002-2008. (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Norfolk, 2004-2008. (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Northumberland County, 2005-2008. (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Nottoway County, 2005-2008. (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Occoquan, 2003-2008. (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Orange County, 2004-2008. (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Page County, 2005-2008. (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Patrick County, 2004-2008. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Petersburg, 2004-2008. (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Poquoson, 2007-2008. (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Portsmouth, 2004-2008. (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Prince Edward County, 2005-2008. (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Prince George County, 2004-2008. (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Prince William County, 2004-2008. (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Pulaski, 2003-2008. (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Pulaski County, 2003-2008. (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Purcellville, 2004-2008. (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Quantico, 2003-2008. (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Rappahannock County, 2003-2008. (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Reedville, Undated. (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Richmond, 2003-2008. (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Richmond County, 2005-2008. (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Roanoke River Rails to Trails, 2005-2008. (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Roanoke River Valley, 2003-2008. (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Robious Elementary School, Richmond, 2004-2008. (Box 64, Folder 39)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Russell County, 2007-2008. (Box 64, Folder 40)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Salem, 2005-2008. (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Saluda, 2005-2008. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Scott County, 2004-2008. (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Scottish Society of Tidewater, 2005-2008. (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Scottsville, 2004-2008. (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Shenandoah, 2003-2008. (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Shenandoah County, 2004-2008. (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Smithfield, 2003-2008. (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Sussex County, 2005-2008. (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Tazewell County, 2005-2008. (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Urbanna, 2004-2008. (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Vienna, 2004-2008. (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Virginia Beach, 2002-2008. (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Virginia Conference Historical Society of the United Methodist Church, 2006-2008. (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Waynesboro, 2006-2008. (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Wellspring United Methodist Church, Williamsburg, 2006-2008. (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - West Point, 2005-2008. (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Westmoreland County, 2005-2008. (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Williamsburg, 2003-2008. (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Winchester, Frederick County, 2003-2008. (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Windsor, 2004-2008. (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Wythe County, 2004-2008. (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Wytheville, 2004-2008. (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - York County, 2002-2008. (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Reports, 2004. (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Reports, 2005. (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Reports, 2006. (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Resource Guide, 2004. (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Resource Guide - Strategic Plan, 2003. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Correspondence - Consultants, Undated. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Correspondence with Communities, 2003. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - DAR Essay Contest, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Early Planning, 2000-2002. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Fall Chairs Meeting, 2004. (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Founder of America Communities, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Genealogy Groups, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Genealogy Groups, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Henricus Colledge, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Heritage Groups, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Heritage Groups, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Heritage Societies, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Historic Brass Music, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Historic Triangle Beautification Awards, 2007. (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Historic Triangle Beautification Awards - James City County, Undated. (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Historic Triangle Beautification Awards - York County, Undated. (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Kickoff/Launch Event - Correspondence, 2003. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Kickoff/Launch Event - Invite, Scheduling, Talking Points, 2003. (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Legislative Reception, 2004. (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Masons, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - NOAA, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Pikemen, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Pikemen & Musketeers, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Press Brochure: Development, Drafts, Final, Undated. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Press Clippings, Undated. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Regional Meetings, 2003. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Regional Meetings, 2004. (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Regional Meetings, 2005. (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Regional Meetings, 2006. (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Regional Meetings, 2007. (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Related Programs, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Richmond Region, 2007. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Speakers Bureau, 1999. (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Speakers Bureau, 2000. (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Speakers Bureau, 2001. (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Speakers Bureau, 2002-2006. (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Speakers Bureau - Summaries, 2001-2006. (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Time Capsule - Correspondence, 2007 April-2008 March. (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Time Capsule - Event, 2009 March 6. (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Time Capsule - Inclusion Items, Undated. (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Time Capsule - Participating Communities, Undated. (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Time Capsule - PowerPoint, Undated. (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Video Correspondence, 2002-2003. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Video Scripts, 2002-2003. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Virginia Film Foundation, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Virginia Music Festival, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Virginia Storytelling Alliance, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Wingfield Family Society, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Series V: Planning Files - Administrative - Historically Significant, 1997-2008., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 72-74)
  Series V: Planning Files contains reports, plans, newsletters, notes, charts, and other sundry items. The series documents the formulation of strategic plans, statewide partners, and national partners.
  - 2007 Heritage Lecture Series, 2000-2007. (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Annual Reports, 2000-2007. (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Arts Council of Richmond-Dominion DX, Undated. (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Economic Impact, 2003-2007. (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Garden Club of Virginia-Tide Radio, Undated. (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Historical Artist (slides), Undated. (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Jamestown 2007 Agency Strategic Plan, Undated. (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Jamestown 2007 Agency Strategic Plan, 1999-2000. (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Jamestown 2007 Agency Strategic Plan - Work Plan, 2002-2003. (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Jamestown 2007 Budgets, 2001-2007. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Jamestown 2007 Newsletter, 1999-2001. (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Jamestown 2007 Office Meeting Notes, 2001. (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Jamestown 2007 Office Meeting Notes, 2001. (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Jamestown 2007 Office Meeting Notes, 2001. (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Jamestown 2007 Organizational Charts, 2005. (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Jamestown 2007 Support Needs, 2003-2004. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Jamestown 2007 Visit to Capitol Hill, 2001-2003. (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Jamestown 2007 Website, 1998-2004. (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - National Council for Social Studies-The Generations Network, Undated. (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - National Flag Festival-Redskins, Undated. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - National Partners, Undated. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Planning an American Celebration Mailing, 1998-1999. (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Statewide Partners - General Information, 1999-2005. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Congress, House Appropriations-Presentations, Report to Virginia General Assembly, 1999-2003. (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - UVA Center For Politics-WXGM Radio, Undated. (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Air & Space-Virginia Business Women, Undated. (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Cattlemen-Virginia Colleges, Undated. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture-Virginia Department of Historical Resources, Undated. (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Department of Mines & Minerals-Virginia Food & Beverage, Undated. (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Genealogical Society-Virginia Hospitality, Undated. (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Library Association-Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Undated. (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Peanut Growers Association-Virginia Telecom, Undated. (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Virtual Jamestown, 1997-1998. (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Willie Cone Appointment - Office Restructure, 2002-2004. (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Series VI: Special Interest Items, 1998-2007., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 75-76)
  Series VI: Special Interest Items contains correspondence, reports, notes, presentations, and other sundry items. This series documents the Virginia Quarter, commemorative stamp & cachet, and the final report of the Jamestown 2007 Steering Committee.
  - American Heritage Flag Pieces, Undated. (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Bermuda Correspondence, 2007. (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Briefing Book, Poster, US Mint Info, Media Schedule, 2003-2005. (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - British Correspondence, 2001-2006. (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Budget and Sponsors, 2003-2005. (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Mint - Jamestown 2007 Staff, 1998-2005. (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (various VIPs), Undated. (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Dick Cheney, 2007. (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - George Bush - Anniversary Weekend, 2007. (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - George Bush - Thanksgiving Proclamation, 2007. (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Godspeed Cachet, 2006-2007. (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Governor Allen, 1997. (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - House Document No. 13, 2009. (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Jamestown 2007 Commemorative Coin, Undated. (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Jamestown 2007 Final Report Steering Committee (hardbound), 2009. (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Jamestown 2007 Final Report Steering Committee (softbound), 2009. (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Jamestown 2007 Stamp and Cachet Project, Undated. (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Kim Scholpp - Archiving Notes, 2008-2009. (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Legislative Activity - Support, Timeline, Bus Tour, 2002-2004. (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - M. Boyd Marcus, 1999. (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Mark R. Warner, 2003-2005. (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - McQuire Woods - Lobby Consultant, Undated. (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Meeting Notes and Newsletters, 2001-2007. (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Norman Beatty Correspondence (CD), 1998. (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Norman Beatty Correspondence (CD), 1998. (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Presentations, 2001-2005. (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Queen Elizabeth Visit, 2007. (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Roxanne Gilmore, 2000. (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Student Art Contest, 2001-2007. (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Timothy Kaine, 2005-2007. (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Quarter - Correspondence, 1998-2000. (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Quarter - Event Ops, Letter to Teachers, 2000. (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Quarter - Keychain for General Assembly Gifts, 2000. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Quarter - Meeting Notes, Fact Sheet, etc., 1998-2000. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - William Clinton, 2007. (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - World Philatelic Expo, 2006. (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Series VII: Correspondence/Subject Files - Agency Heads, 1997-2007., Extent: 1 box. (Box 77)
  Series VII: Correspondence/Subject Files - Agency Heads contains correspondence and other sundry items belonging to Norman Beatty, William Cone, & Jeanne Zeidler who served as executive directors of Jamestown 2007 from 1997 to 2007.
  - Norman Beatty, 1997-1998. (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Norman Beatty, 1999-2000. (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Norman Beatty, 2001. (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Norman Beatty, 2002. (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Norman Beatty, 2003-2005. (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - William Cone, 2003-2004. (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Jeanne Zeidler, 2002-2003. (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Jeanne Zeidler, 2004-2007. (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Series VIII: Correspondence/Subject Files - Other Officials, 1996-2007., Extent: 1 box. (Box 78)
  Series VIII: Correspondence/Subject Files - Other Officials contains correspondence and other sundry items belonging to Jamestown 2007 senior staff including Amy Ritchie and Steering Committee Chairman Stuart Connock.
  - Colin Campbell, 2002-2006. (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Committee - V. Earl Dickinson, H. Benson Dendy, Horace Mann, Thomas Norment, 2002-2006. (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Committees, Undated. (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Frank Atkinson, 2000-2007. (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Jamestown 2007 Office Staff - Amy Ritchie, 2001-2002. (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Jamestown 2007 Office Staff - Amy Ritchie, 2003-2007. (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Jamestown 2007 Office Staff - Patrick Brennan, Anne Dale, Howard Gervertz, Drema Johnson, Avis Tucker, Gloria Warren, 1999-2007. (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Jamestown 2007 Office Staff - Ross Richardson, 2003-2006. (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Jamestown 2007 Office Staff - Victor Clough, 2003-2005. (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Stuart Connock, 1996-2000. (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Stuart Connock, 2001-2007. (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Suzanne Flippo, 1999-2002. (Box 78, Folder 7)